Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! (A Man After Midnight)
Half past twelve
And I'm watching the late show in my flat all alone
How I hate to spend the evening on my own
Autumn winds
Blowing outside the window as
I look around the room
And it makes me so depressed to see the gloom
There's not a soul out there no one to hear my prayer
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
Won't somebody help me chase the shadows away?
Take me through the darkness to the break of the day
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
Movie stars
Find the end of the rainbow with a fortune to win
It's so different from the world
I'm living in
Tired of
T.V. I open the window and
I gaze into the night
But there's nothing there to see no one in sight
There's not a soul out there no one to hear my prayer
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
Won't somebody help me chase the shadows away?
Take me through the darkness to the break of the day
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
There's not a soul out there no one to hear my prayer
Won't somebody help me chase the shadows away?
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
Take me through the darkness to the break of the day
Won't somebody help me chase the shadows away?
Gimme gimme gimme a man after midnight
Take me through the darkness to the break of the day